nude-celebrities-network.com 2014-06-03

# Privacy Policy of Lotus Asia Casino Best Online Casino Gaming

Lotus Asia Casino is committed to protect your personal information. We have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you use our services at our online sites. We are dedicated to safeguard and protect the privacy of the Players.

Privacy is fundamental to every being and at Lotus Asia Casino we respect your privacy and security to the utmost. It is our deepest Endeavour to ensure that your privacy is preserved at all times unless we are driven by law to reveal any wrongdoing. We are sticklers for truth and honesty and have no patience for criminals and cheats. Upholding your privacy is our duty and we ensure you are protected at all times.

For the purpose of business, we gather essential information such as your name, residential address, contact number, email id, debit/credit card data, date of birth, other vital information and all this is collected at the time of registration. We also save your voice sample but do not hold it in our records as we want no discrepancy creeping in at any time. This information is important so as to notify you as regards the launch of new products, services or software. Being updated with the latest is crucial else you will not be able to keep pace with other players on board. We offer gambling services to you once all data is completed. This information also helps us to respond to your queries and requests. Offering member support is vital and we are able to execute the same only if we have complete knowledge about your personal facts.

Your information may be disclosed to other companies and employees associated with Lotus Asia Casino. Auditors, contractors and advisors of the company may also be privy to your personal information. Investors in the company and purchasers may require your information. Keep in mind that we have rules, security policies as well as practical measures to safeguard your information and our personnel as well as data processors that have access to this information, are obliged to respect the same.

This personal information is collected by us at the time you register and commence using our gambling services. At Lotus Asia Casino we believe that it’s urgent to make inquiries concerning members so that we are able to sustain a clean record. We begin collecting information when you respond to our emails and/or generally begin communications with us. All your documentation and information is safe with us and you will receive emails from our registered domain LotusAsiaCasino.com e.g. 

support@lotusasiacasino.com. Please feel free to unsubscribe in case you are not interested in receiving any emails from us.

We are grateful that you have chosen to game here. In case you need help, contact support@lotusasiacasino.com, call us via phone, online live help or visit our About Us. We thank you for choosing and placing your trust in Lotus Asia Casino.
